welcome to mr. beast gaming my arm is
cut off it's very painful and in today's
video we were giving away $10,000 here's
how Chris hit a button I like that one
oh my gosh see how the blocks are
disappearing every time he hits a button
but when all the blocks disappear they
fall in lava last person alive wins
eNOS with like 10 presses alright yeah
I'm feeling I'm feeling a Teddy a 9/10
oh okay oh these guys are stuck in a
hole and to make things even more
interesting coral and Chandler are
competing they are in survival mode and
they're just like everyone else
all these kids it's getting pretty
skimpy out here it's getting very scary
very soon yeah
don't forget boys $10,000 oh my god poor
him here's the block under him can break
and there could be just a giant hole hey
I don't know what you were gonna try to
get this 10 grand Carl yeah sorry what
oh you did that on your own
Carl look right here in the middle of
the behemoth Taylor diner okay so do
Carl's I didn't fall Jimmy pushed me
guys get me out it's boy Jedi in this
let's see if he's it easier somewhere
and here's boy Jedi who won this video
there's Bourget ID this guy's the one
currently in the lead Thank You Jedi
I'll get you your 10 grand if he wins
another 10 grand that's crazy like he
he's try harder he's strafing the entire
time he almost won the other one too
let's see if I can get him out with
these are you pressing buttons oh oh oh
oh my gosh dude I'm button hungry hungry
chillers two blocks away from dying
already hey this guy's the president's
kid you know we gotta save him yeah that
means we've got well agreed there would
be hitting buttons oh no that was me
sorry I'm sorry you just killed that guy
yeah depressants good mr. beast gaming
is the number one minecraft channel
Chris give me jump boost
give me jump please come on
Jayla no no no no get out of there
what is this a feather what could you
can fly with it just fly for your arms
really hard
hahahahaha thanks buddy oh look Carl if
I broke this block you could get up yes
completely but that would be cheating
wait cheating like how you pushed me to
the ravine I'm getting hungry again oh
my gosh you're going oh my gosh there
dude like there's only half the buns
left Chris Oh back up baby nope oh I
just fell I just fell again so far these
are all the people that I've gotten out
oh I'm sorry cute double oh this is the
guy I killed I feel that he probably
hates me I'm almost back up okay there's
no way I'm getting back up though no I'm
literally about a beer so these are all
the buttons we have left I got button
Hungary I'm sorry permission to take my
own blocks away sir you can do one i won
hahaha you didn't even get them that's
two
Hey oh I'm good I'm back up top baby are
you really oh wow you are how'd you get
Chandler get up top but you can listen
man all right I'll go but mash sorry I
like mostly whoopee for today hey I'm at
the top what if I accidentally press the
button right underneath you Carl oh my
god oh wow Carl wow it actually hit the
BOK under you I don't I'm pressing some
buttons
oh boy Jedi's at the bottom of the map
wait why isn't he he's a hacker Kickham
ban him from the store I got you a slash
ban Fox gaming
ban hammer stick together Carl what the
heck I'm not dying that dude was not
hack oh you know I'm dying yeah no
you're not sir you're telling me we
banned a guy that was an actor no we
just don't know how our map works
alright we're sorry that guy that kid
was about to cries to sleep tonight
he was so innocently he just stared at
us with cute I waited he was a little
cute little fox boy alright you know
what I think we make things a little
interesting no I don't think so I think
we're fine I think a creepers about to
spawn up top don't sell no one know how
walking around so well I can't even
Traverse this land this we'll all right
there's creepers everywhere oh poor guy
you got hit by two wow that seems like
quite enough creepers guys oh gosh Jimmy
there's a my hero skin down here I spot
a creep I'm gonna put lunch in one spot
in the middle creeper creeper party
oh look Jimmy all these people are right
here be a shame if somebody just put a
creeper right there creeper game paper
game alright everybody so far about a
dozen of you have gotten out it's about
to get really hard I just wanted to
remind you that $10,000 is on the line
I'm gonna purposely go after you cuz you
didn't help me at all no Chandler I
tried to help you when what when do you
not remember when you were dying I was
literally coming towards you I was
trying to find you I don't believe it
Chandler you want to go press five
buttons three oh my god oh yeah what if
we filled the bottom layer with creepers
mom and what it's the only time I win on
this freakin channel is against a
hundred people are you still in what
about the top layer baby
Carl watch out this guy like with
somebody threw an egg right girl for ten
minutes
show all right Kayla go go pop five more
one two three oh my good night oh
they're begging us to stop the creeper
hey winning ten grand isn't supposed to
be easy
five more someone fell to my place hope
we lost another one how are they falling
is good no oh no dummy died okay so
they're all fallen Jedi you didn't get
another 10 grand sorry buddy I learn
about Jedi feels I mean he won 10 grand
so I don't feel bad but he also lost
thirty thousand dollars to the last week
Hey look you win some you lose some
yeah or you could be like Carl and you
just lose them all yeah hey Hubble right
now I'm killing it guys did I hear
dump a bucket of lava on Carl I'll
monitor Carl hi I monitor alone to
monitor Carl doink doink doink oh my
gosh oh my gosh this guy's doing a full
parkour dude he got back up watchdog
nice he's sweaty right now oh he made it
2:03 dude
one down two down well stuck you have to
park or to get up do you trust your
parkour skills enough no I don't know if
you remember I suck at parkour just one
person really down below and that can
now get up it oh yeah he can't get up
planes though there we go if he's really
good he can get back up I'm gonna put
creepers isolated in the middle to make
this even more fun all groupers are Oh
creepers are jumping people are dropping
everything's dropping I think it's time
Chandler five buttons ready for three oh
my gosh 200 people are following right
four people just died these people need
to get off my block the creepers are
starting to work their way up because
the buttons are like disappearing
pathways for them and they're just
walking up and blowing up people from
the bottom all right so here's what I'm
doing Chris given them a water Pole oh
wait I didn't contain it it's gonna
break some of the lava whoops mmm the
waterfall did not go as planned
Oh a creeper is going after somebody all
this crispers going after this kid oh he
just disappeared what the heck how many
buttons should i press a lot oh oh
people are falling oh my gosh Chris you
just killed four people
I'm so sorry I feel terrible I'm sorry
that I ruined your chances children
there are now ten ones
laughs each button represents ten
percent the remaining blocks Chandler go
press two buttons no Carl this is all
about the in soon I'm hitting one one oh
my gosh no that was my escape route to
the wake let's go give us three Chandler
Oh Robin all these people just lost
Chris go get rid of 25% of the blocks
I Oh No here I go five buttons somebody
kick out one no there were five buttons
not for a twenty five percent of five
visit three what is it
one no what would one mess
Oh what you do how many there's two
buttons so Chris click one of them again
what money
so what you're hypothetically you're
gonna kill half the people are ready
right here go up dive spawn a creeper
run button oh five one two three four
five six seven eight nine ten so wait if
you press this last button one they all
just die well let's just find out yeah
here wait love these guys oh is that
everybody
oh there's no oh
all right dirt soon 0:05 picked the
$10,000 plot you just won 10 grand let's
talk about discord are you jur to 0:05
yes I am
congratulations you got $10,000 Oh
oh my god yes sir wait how old are you
I'm 14 when you're 14 crap geez at 14
he's made more money in challenges than
I yes he's very epic I know
okay everybody subscribe to mr. B's
gaming it now
yeah next time your parents tell you
that you have to get off for the night
tell them you can win $10,000 so you're
not going to do goodbye before you go I
just want to say real quick if you win
one of these challenges and you're under
18 years old we're gonna need to get
your parents permission before we send
the money but we will send it